Today friends let's talk about piles, hemorrhoids, mass, that is, the
problem of the android. If you have pain,
bleeding, swelling, when we check and
tell a person that operation is necessary, then many times a common question
comes that brother, how soon should this operation be done?
If your doctor or your partner has
told you after checkup that
operation is necessary, then how soon can the operation be done?
Perhaps you have some important office work
or some auction, some such
wedding matter, or some
important family function and
you have to attend that too, then when should an
operation be done? Is it
urgent, is it an emergency, or
can it be done later? So friends, this
is a very important and useful video. If you are
suffering from piles or hemorrhoids
and if you need surgery, then
when can this operation be done, how can it be done,
and when is it necessary to do it. Do like,
share, subscribe. Let's start
this video. So friends, if someone is
suffering from piles, then the three symptoms
which are present in the problem  There are pain, bleeding and swelling,
these are the three most important symptoms or
symptoms which are relief, out of which
if you are suffering from a lot, like pain
is actually pain, after passing stool
you have a very high fever for an hour or two
or the bleeding is
very heavy like a squirt and that
bleeding is so much that you are probably
losing blood as well, then these two problems are such
problems which indicate an early need for surgery, that is, if
your pain is severe and you have
tried diets, medicines, ointments and you are
not getting relief from it, then operation is
definitely necessary, if your blood is decreasing a lot,
like your hemoglobin has become
5-6 and due to that you may have problems in your
heart, you may feel dizzy, you may fall, then
you are definitely at risk of getting injured in it suddenly, so
if your
hemoglobin is low 5-6 and this 56 is
due to piles mass, then also you
must get an operation as soon as possible, the third one is
pain relief or symptom relief  And there is Sujan, that is,
great, Sujan is stuck outside,
this Sujan is very much and this Sujan is
causing you some disco fat,
but this problem of yours is the problem of Sujan, it is the
problem of swelling, but if this
swelling is minor for you or there is a little discomfort, then
you can pull it a little,
like if your office is running less important, some
trip is going on or there is some
other family event, auction,
some marriage ceremony and it is
very important for you to attend it and it is urgent, then you
can pull it a little,
you get some relief from medicine or ointment, so if there is
more discomfort in Sujan's pain, then the operation
which I am telling you is a reality of the situation and
bleeding is very much, then operation is
definitely necessary,
when is the relief to do the operation and how soon is it
necessary to do it, there is no definition or
timeline in this because the
triviality of symptoms of different people is different,
secondly your reports are also different,
these are different and the
timeline is according to your expectation.  Surely there is
no such fixed criteria definition, it is a relief but it should be done as soon as possible, should it be done
quickly or can be done slowly,
it depends on whether your files are
thrombotic or not, how much pain you have, whether there is
any infection there or whether
your hemoglobin is low or not or how much
you have been suffering from this problem for so long, even if you have
tried a lot,
you still have the need to do the operation quickly,
if you have not tried and the
problem is minor then you can try once,
from diet to medicine to ointment,
take advice under the guidance of the doctor so that
your treatment is safe, so do
subscribe by liking the video, I hope
that you get useful information from our video,
if you are suffering from fever or
hemorrhage, then the symptoms of your problem are
big, please type it in the comment area